barco.com.cn 2018-05-24

# Privacy - Barco

Your privacy is important to us. This is the Privacy policy of the websites of Barco NV and its subsidiaries (“Barco”). Barco NV is a public limited liability company incorporated under Belgian law, with registered office at President Kennedypark 35, 8500 Kortrijk, Belgium.

This Privacy policy can be modified, e.g. as a result of new functionalities on the Barco websites that require the processing of personal data. We thus advise you to check this Privacy policy regularly. Any major changes will be notified via our website. 

This policy should be read together with Barco’s [cookie policy](https://www.barco.com/about-barco/legal/cookie-policy).

This version of the Privacy policy was modified on April 19, 2018. ****

  * When does this Privacy policy apply?
  * Who is responsible for the processing of your personal data?
  * Which personal data do we process about you?
  * For what purposes do we process your personal data?
  * Who has access to your personal data?
  * What about links to other websites and social media?
  * How long do we keep your personal data?
  * How are your personal data protected?
  * What are your rights and how can you exercise them?

## When does this Privacy policy apply?

This Privacy policy applies to the processing of personal data obtained via the websites of Barco.

## Who is responsible for the processing of your personal data?

Barco is the party responsible for the processing of your personal data. This means that Barco determines for what purposes and with what means your personal data will be processed.

Barco has appointed a Data Protection Officer (DPO) who will be your point of contact for any questions or requests regarding the processing of your personal data. The contact details of the DPO can be found under point 9 of this Privacy policy.

## Which personal data do we process about you?

We collect your personal data in three ways:

### a. Information provided by you

We receive your information in the first place if you share it with us by:

  * contacting us via the contact form
  * filling in a form on our website
  * creating a “myBarco” account
  * requesting content or software (e.g. brochures or drivers)
  * signing up for email communications 
  * participating in a survey
  * ordering a product online
  * logging a ticket for technical questions (“eSupport”)
  * asking for service support
  * applying for our certified training program
  * registering our products (for remote connectivity)

In these cases, we usually receive information such as your first name, last name, e-mail address, telephone number, address details (street, number, postcode, city, country), the project or the region in which you are interested, your position, your correspondence with Barco, your partner types, your market and application segments and other personal and/ or contact details.

### b. Automatically obtained information

When you browse our website, we receive data from cookie providers about your activity on our website such as the time and duration of your visit, the hyperlinks that you clicked which brought you to our website and the hyperlinks on our website which link to other websites, your IP address, the pages you visit, the browser you use, geographical data such as your location and your preferred language. 

We do this by using cookies. More information on the use of cookies by Barco can be found in our [cookie policy](https://www.barco.com/about-barco/legal/cookie-policy). 

### c. Information obtained from third parties

Sometimes we also receive your information from affiliated companies or from professional data suppliers. 

If you are an end user of a Barco product, we may collect your data if a dealer provides your information in the context of promotions or business opportunities. 

## For what purposes do we process your personal data?

### a. In order to respond to your requests and keep you informed

We process your personal data when you request a brochure, order a product, ask to be kept informed of our activities, projects, offers, events, actions and so on.

For this purpose we may process data such as your name, your address, your e-mail address, your telephone number, your preferred language and the project or the region in which you are interested.

These data are processed on the basis of your unambiguous consent, the performance of a contract to which you are a party, or your request to take steps prior to entering into a contract. 

If you have previously sent us a request to receive a brochure or ordered a product, we will keep you informed about our products. All our emails contain an “unsubscribe” button. You can also contact our DPO at any time for more information (see point 9 of the Privacy Policy in connection with your right to object).

### b. In order to answer your questions and exchange information

If you ask us questions by telephone or e-mail, we will process your personal data in order to respond to your question.

For this purpose we may process data such as your name, your company name, your position, your e-mail address, your telephone number, your correspondence with Barco and all other personal data that you provide to us that can be relevant for answering your question.

These data are processed on the basis of your request to take steps prior to entering a contract, the performance of a contract to which you are a party, or Barco’s legitimate interest in informing you about its activities. 

### c. In order to set up and manage a myBarco account

We process personal data when you create a personal myBarco account. When you sign into your myBarco account, we create a record of your sign-in, which includes the date and time, your sign-in name and the unique number assigned to your account. Signing into your account enables improved personalization, the possibility to follow a Barco training, ask for service support and other enhanced features and settings.

For this purpose we may process data such as your name, your e-mail address, your telephone number, your preferred language, your company name, your Barco contact, your partner types and your market and application segments. 

These data are processed on the basis of your unambiguous consent, your request to take steps prior to entering a contract, the performance of a contract to which you are a party or Barco’s legitimate interest in informing you about its activities.

### d. For the technical and functional management of our websites

We process personal data for the technical and functional management of our websites, in order to personalise the websites and to ensure that the websites are easy to use. 

For this purpose we may process data such as your IP address, the pages you visit, the browser you use, the websites you visited earlier, geographical data such as your location, your preferred language and the time and duration of your visit. 

These data are processed on the basis of your unambiguous consent or Barco’s legitimate interest in improving its websites and protecting itself against cyber-attacks.

## Who has access to your personal data?

Barco can share your data with other companies associated with Barco. In addition, Barco calls upon third parties to perform certain (processing) activities, such as hosting the websites. 

We may share your personal data with certain third parties:

  * processors who act on our behalf, such as e.g. marketing and communication companies;
  * business partners with whom we carry out joint promotions or programs;
  * business partners who provide service support;
  * IT service providers that provide technical support;
  * payment service providers;
  * attorneys and external advisors: in certain cases Barco may transfer your personal data to attorneys and external advisors if this  is necessary to give us advice or to defend our rights;
  * supervisory authorities in case of a lawful request;
  * possible acquirers of the whole or part of Barco in the event that (a part of) our activities would be taken over by a third party.

Barco is committed to always ensuring an adequate and sufficient level of protection for your data. If you have any questions or would like more information about the transfer of your personal data outside the European Economic Area, you can send an email to [dataprotection@barco.com](mailto:dataprotection@barco.com).

Personal data are not provided to other parties, unless required by law or pursuant to a court order.

The websites of Barco can contain references (e.g. via hyperlinks) to other websites, which are offered by third parties. Barco is not responsible for the processing of personal data via these websites.  Barco advices you to check the privacy policies of these websites. This privacy policy applies only to the Barco websites. 

If you share content from the Barco websites via social media, this content will be visible for the visitors of these social media. Barco is not responsible for the processing of personal data via these social media.  This privacy policy applies only to the Barco websites. 

## How long do we keep your personal data?

Barco will retain your personal data for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

If no legal retention period applies, Barco will process your data at least as long as it has a contractual relationship with you.

## How are your personal data protected?

Barco strives to protect your personal data by means of technical and organisational measures, such as firewalls and secured servers that may only be accessed by a limited number of persons holding special access rights and with respect to the nature of the data.

Despite these measures, due care should be taken when storing and/or sharing your personal data and login, particularly when connecting via unsecure or public networks.

## What are your rights and how can you exercise them?

You have a number of rights with regard to your personal data, such as the right of access, the right to rectification of inaccurate personal data, the right to erasure or restriction of processing, the right to data portability, the right not to be subject to profiling and the right to object to the processing. Some of these rights have a very specific scope or are subject to special conditions or exceptions. Please contact our DPO for any questions or requests regarding the processing of your personal data ([dataprotection@barco.com](mailto:dataprotection@barco.com)).

If the processing of your data is based on consent, you also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, without this affecting the legitimacy of the processing done prior to the withdrawal of your consent. You can send an e-mail to [dataprotection@barco.com](mailto:dataprotection@barco.com) or by post to the below mentioned address or you can visit the [unsubscribe page](https://infopages.barco.com/Unsubscribe-Page.html) on our website. Barco cannot process your request without proof of your identity.

You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of an alleged infringement. The Belgian Data Protection Authority is the supervisory authority for Belgium and can be contacted at [commission@privacycommission.be](mailto:commission@privacycommission.be).

If you have any further questions or complaints about the processing of your personal data, about Barco’s websites or about this Privacy Policy you can always contact us:

  * by e-mail at [dataprotection@barco.com](mailto:dataprotection@barco.com); or
  * by phone at the number +32 56 26 2215 
  * by mail to:  
Barco – Data Protection Officer  
Beneluxpark 21  
8500 Kortrijk, Belgium
